Hello Hello Friends Welcome
to Payment Voucher So in this video we will
talk about three main points of SBI Life stock. The first thing will be that some people
ask me in the comment section about
making the SBI Life stock that it had
fallen yesterday and it has fallen today as well. So many
people were under the influence. So first thing is that some
people have this doubt that the
EP ratio is falling because of this topic. Let's
discuss this. We will discuss this
on two issues. The first issue will be
what is behind the industry and the second is their legacy from their
peers for generations.
Second we will talk about their fundamentals which we keep discussing
often and the third thing which we
will discuss is the main topic of this video,
why is the correction visible. So if you are watching this for the
first time, please subscribe to our detailed channel.
Watch this video.
You will get to know a lot about this York
stock.
Today if we talk about SBI Life, it
is down at 1.40 and this correction has come, so
now we will have to accept that yes there is a
correction but with them SBI
Life  There is another reason for the correction with ,
I will explain that reason at the end of the video. If
you want, you can definitely skip the video and
watch it. See, after reaching 1273,
it has shown a continuous correction. If we
talk about today, are many people running away in the midst of this decline?
See, 10 lakh
shares were traded in which
delivery was taken from 5 lakh 75 thousand. At the time I am
making the video, it is now
03:19 in the afternoon. There are still 11 minutes left for the market to close.
Yesterday also, i.e. on 7th October, delivery of cents
was visible at 67. That means, yesterday also a
good amount of sales were taken in the midst of the decline.
But when the decline started, you can see that on
6th October, 43 percent trading was visible here at 57.
One of the main reasons for the decline with this hair is that this is a
bit unlucky stock. Unlucky in the sense.
Whenever there is a good rise in the stock, if you
want a good leg, then some
big institutional buyer sells and exits.
Here, who is the institutional outsider
who has sold and exited, you will get to know its data
in the coming few days, so
we do not get to know the data of institutional buyers who sell and leave immediately,
this is the rule of NSC,
but you can see here that the
delivery percentage has remained constant, now
coming to the fundamentals, 1 lakh
21500 is a company worth 36 crores, it is a large cap
company,
after making only 1234, correction
is visible, this topic P 94.4, here we
talk about this topic, many people are
confused in this, that is, the stock which is behind,
Industries Pet 600,
800, that is, the stock which is
more than Industries Pet, that is, the stock of this industry,
you should roughly understand that the period
U means how much money someone wants to pay to buy a share of ₹1, so
here you understand that after seeing 26.8, one wants to buy the
city of this industry, whereas SBI Life by
paying ₹90, but  Is this the speed,
how should it be? Not all stickers. Here you
can see DSC Life Insurance Company whose
stop is 124, ICICI Prudential
whose stock is 202 and my favorite company
in this sector is New India Insurance
whose stock is also only 19.10. There are
opportunities in this company.
If we talk about sales, then SBI
Life is a very big brand and a very
big elephant. We can clearly see the sales of this sector.
Compared to 2020, almost
double, active growth of seven percent is
visible.
Your expenses are also visible in the same countries.
Due to this, there has been no big jump in the net profit here.
You can see here that the
net profit of SBI Life is
1327 crore, 1422 crore in 2019 and 1456 crore in 2021.
But we know that the 2020 decline has
not been very good for this sector
because due to quality the situation has worsened. If we
talk about research, then 9578
crore  Reserves of Rs 1000 crore are lying unused till 2021. Now when the
September results come, the picture will become
clearer for you. Reserve Bank, now it is a
matter of fact that you will see high
returns,
whereas if we talk about its borrowing and debt, then there is a debt of
zero rupees. The
company is DF.
Hey, you can see the questions that people asked on the site, on the
strength of RSS,
after today I see Gift going up to
50. The
buffer stock for MI is looking great.
I am also up ten center on Shirdi signal
and you can see cheap here, the MACD
signal is light, this means the stock is
currently showing weakness from its actual value.
Now,
speaking of those who trade, I feel that
you can take this 50-day as a stop loss
and this 50-day will also become your strong
support. Those who
want to take it a little lower can merge with 1150,
but if there is a fall below this, then
you may also see labels of 1070.
Those who watch these charts etc.
This is not for investors,
I never advise you to trade.
I feel that the
target being told is 13, 1350,
it will easily become good by the end of October
and in March 2022, i.e. next
financial year, you will see SBI Life making a
surplus of 17 and I am telling this
target keeping in mind their industry growth and their
sales and profit growth.
Do tell me in the comment box how you liked the video, do click on the first
and service tab, thank you for
watching.